{
    "questions":
        [
            {
                "question": "What is the output of the code? alert(typeof(NaN));",
                "choices": ["number", "object", "string", "function"],
                "type": "radio",
                "correctAnswer": "number"
            },
            {
                "question": "You can’t delete variables declared with var keyword by ‘delete’ operator.",
                "choices": ["true", "false"],
                "type": "radio",
                "correctAnswer": "true"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output of the code? alert(typeof([1, 2]) != (typeof {obg:23}));",
                "choices": ["true", "false"],
                "type": "radio",
                "correctAnswer": "false"
            },
            {
                "question": "JS numbers are always stored as double precision floating point numbers.",
                "choices": ["true", "false"],
                "type": "radio",
                "correctAnswer": "true"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output of the code?",
                "description": "alert(0.1 + 0.2 == 0.3);",
                "choices": ["true", "false"],
                "type": "radio",
                "correctAnswer": "false"
            },
            {
                "question": "What function is used to merge arrays?",
                "choices": ["concat()", "merge()", "array_merge()", "add()"],
                "type": "radio",
                "correctAnswer": "concat()"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output?",
                "description": "function mlt(a, b) {<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;if(!(a && b)) {<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;return 0;<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;} else if(b == 1) {<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;return a;<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;} else {<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;return (a + mlt(a, b - 1));<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;}<br>}<br>console.log(mlt(3, 11));<br>console.log(mlt(7, 1));",
                "type": "input",
                "correctAnswer": "337"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output?",
                "description": "(function(){alert(typeof arguments);})();",
                "choices": ["object", "function", "undefined", "null"],
                "type": "radio",
                "correctAnswer": "object"
            },
            {
                "question": "Choose the numbers that are present in the output.",
                "description": "for(let i = 0; i < 100; i ++)<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;if(i % 10 == i - 10)<br>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;document.write(i + ',');",
                "choices": ["14", "17", "27", "9"],
                "type": "select",
                "correctAnswer": ["14", "17"]
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output?",
                "description": "var a = 5 && 8;<br>var b = 5 || 8;<br>console.log(a + b);",
                "type": "input",
                "correctAnswer": "13"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output?",
                "description": "typeof(NaN);",
                "type": "input",
                "correctAnswer": "number"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output?",
                "description": "console.log((true+false)>2+true);",
                "choices": ["true", "false", "error"],
                "type": "radio",
                "correctAnswer": "false"
            }
        ]
}
